Bro.
You're in for telecom fraud too, right?
The food here is terrible.
There's no spice in it at all.
Bro, where are you from?
You wouldn't know even if I told you.
Lingchuan County.
You're from Lingchuan County too?
Do you know Fang Quan?
Even if our county is small,
I couldn't possibly know everyone.
Fang Quan?
Is he a friend of yours?
He worked at the parts factory over there.
Oh, the parts factory.
My cousin used to work there too.
They had to work from dawn to dusk.
Always rushing around just to eat or use the bathroom.
If you got sleepy and dozed off,
your hand would get chopped right off by the machine.
Then the factory would just kick you out.
They really are a Heartless bunch.
Let me do it.
Okay, thanks, bro.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's just a bit gross.
You seem pretty used to it.
We only do this when we're on duty.
But my mom does this out there every day.
Hello?
Get to the hospital quickly.
Lu's father isn't going to make it!
What did you say?
Old Lu, wake up.
Old Lu, please wake up.
What happened?
My poor Old Lu.
There was no one at home.
I don't know how he fell.
By the time he was found, he was already...
You can't go.
How am I going to explain this to Little Yong?
Lu's mother.
Please sit down.
My poor Old Lu.
How could he abandon the two of us?
He just left...
...just like that.
How do I explain this to Little Yong?
When Old Lu was brought in for emergency treatment,
he was holding onto this the whole time.
They said he was trying to reach for this photo
when he fell out of bed.
Lao Kong told me
about Xiao Lu's father.
Are you
trying to get the Detention Center to release him
to attend his father's memorial service?
As for me,
I'd advise you not to waste your effort.
If Xiao Lu gets out right now,
it will only shake his resolve.
Besides, the higher-ups have explicitly told you
to wrap it up quickly.
So,
at a time like this, you really shouldn't
be causing trouble for us
and Zhao Yijie,
okay?
And this
is a little something from me.
Please pass it on to Lu's mother.
Little Yong.
Mom.
Why do you look so tired?
Didn't you say the new job was easy?
I'm not tired.
Mom was moving,
that's why I'm tired.
Let me show you pictures of the new house.
Look.
This is our new home.
This...
This is the kitchen.
See? The furniture and all...
It's all there.
I can see it.
Why isn't Dad in the photos?
The results of the psychiatric evaluation are out.
You are perfectly normal.
At the time of the incident,
your actual age was only 13.
Under the Criminal Law,
in a situation like yours,
you may face massive civil compensation,
but won't bear criminal liability.
However,
starting from March of last year,
the Criminal Law Amendment
has established further provisions.
Even if you are 13,
if the Supreme People's Procuratorate approves it
and determines this case involves aggravated circumstances,
you will still bear criminal liability.
If it really comes to that,
it means fixed-term imprisonment of at least 10 years or life imprisonment,
or even the death penalty.
The death penalty?
That's not what he said before!
Who told you otherwise?
And what exactly did he say?
"Little Yong is only 13.
He won't have to pay with his life for murder."
Of course,
I will try my best
to prevent the worst-case scenario.
But as your defense counsel,
both the best and worst-case scenarios...
I have an obligation to tell you.
Then it will be up to you,
Lu Zhiyong,
to make a decision.
Decide what?
He is still a child.
Talk to me if there's anything.
You really need to reflect on your actions.
You have no idea
how hard it is for your mother out there.
She didn't just get this tired from moving.
She's actually tired from taking care of your father.
And I am sorry to tell you
that your father passed away three days ago.
Lawyer Ding!
And the people you grit your teeth
and desperately try to protect
wouldn't even let me fight for
a brief release for you
so you could attend your father's cremation.
So, Lu Zhiyong,
is what you're going through really worth it?
Think about it carefully.
Lawyer Ding.
Have some water and calm down.
We're all just
concerned about the kid.
Thank you for your trouble.
Fan Dong barging in last time
was a special exception I made.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself in there.
Mom will wait for you to come out.
Hello, I'm here to pick up my phone.
Ding Ning.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm a police officer from the Zhongshan Road Police Station.
Do you know Mr. Yu Songfan?
Thanks.
For what?
Let me tell you,
their whole enforcement process was problematic.
Forgetting my ID
is absolutely not
a reason for them to restrict my freedom.
Alright, stop complaining.
Where did you park the car?
The parking lot.
Where else would I park it?
Okay, then let's go to the parking lot.
I already told you,
I just drove out to buy groceries.
And as a result,
I ran into that cop checking IDs.
I didn't have it on me,
so they called you.
You drove just to buy groceries?
And they also said
you got lost.
You didn't look right,
and couldn't remember your ID number,
so they kindly took you to the station.
Then they looked through your phone,
found my phone number,
and asked me to come pick you up.
Forget it, let's drop it.
Stop talking about it, please.
You're making it sound like
I really can't take care of myself.
Alright, alright, they made a mountain out of a molehill.
It's not your fault, alright?
What about your hand?
When are you getting the stitches out?
It's fine.
Just superficial wounds. It's nothing.
Let's just find the car first, okay?
Stop talking to me.
I can't be answering your questions
while trying to find the car.
I'm telling you, it's on this floor.
Alright, alright, I won't speak.
I won't say a word, okay?
I'm telling you,
I remember it's definitely on this floor.
Do you remember which color it was?
Here.
I told you.
I remember.
Right, right, right.
It's right here.
Alright, found it.
This parking lot's layout is just terrible.
Seriously.
Here, let me drive.
I want to practice driving.
I haven't driven in a long time.
It's not like I have Parkinson's.
I can drive myself.
I know.
I just want some practice.
You can be my instructor.
The investigation won't happen overnight.
You still need to get some rest.
I know you're having a hard time.
If there's anything you want to say,
just tell me.
Right by that supermarket.
Pull over up ahead.
I'll go buy some bread
for Awu's breakfast tomorrow.
He has school.
Awu is at Zhao Yijie's house.
I always thought
even if I forgot everything,
the people and things important to me,
I would
keep etched in my mind.
But now...
I know
there will come a day
when I see Awu
and won't remember who he is.
I'll forget Awu's name,
forget him entirely,
and eventually forget you, too.
Don't be so pessimistic.
I know I don't have much time left.
Before I forget everything,
I need to make sure you're settled.
Lao Yu,
don't worry.
If that day really comes,
Awu and I will both be just fine.
Trust me.
I trust you.
And I believe you'll take good care of Awu.
But I don't trust Zhao Yijie.
You know?
I'm just afraid that one day,
I'll forget that bastard.
Forget all the evil he's done.
I wish I could personally
strike the gavel to judge him.
But I know I won't live to see that day.
I really thought about killing him.
And then killing Bi Wenhao, right?
Think about it.
You know the law.
You know
the court can't possibly try a sick man like me.
They can't do anything to me.
Fine, even if it means
spending the rest of my life in prison,
so what?
My mind
is already a complete mess.
In a prison, in a nursing home,
or anywhere else, it makes no difference.
I can no longer undo my mistakes.
Most importantly,
I'll even forget who I am.
In the end, I won't even feel guilty about murder.
Isn't this the best solution,
the best ending?
Right?
Lao Yu...
Let's go home first.
Let's go home, okay?
We'll talk about it at home.
Listen to me.
Let's go home.
Come on, let's go home.
Right, I have something to give you at home.
I forgot again.
Right, let's go home.
It's fine.
I was looking for a piece of evidence,
so I rummaged through the whole house.
I finally found it.
It's a dashcam.
It should help with Xiao Lu's case.
I think I put it in the safe.
Let me go get it for you now.
I have something that would make a great greeting gift.
What?
A dashcam.
I told you,
the Holdout's surveillance footage
isn't with me.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Lao Yu has a dashcam.
Even he can't remember where he put it.
To find it,
I gave Lao Yu a cash dividend.
Inside the cash box,
I placed a Tracker.
But after tracking it,
I realized the dashcam
wasn't kept with the cash.
It might be in that safe.
But if it really is in there,
Lao Yu must be on guard against me.
So I didn't touch the safe.
You go find it.
And bring this dashcam
back to us.
Can you do it?
What's wrong?
Can't open it?
I forgot the password.
Don't worry.
Do you usually follow a pattern for your passwords?
Like your phone number,
important dates, or a birthday or something?
It's still wrong.
We've tried them all.
Look, your wedding anniversary,
your birthday, your wife's birthday,
Yu Xiaoyue's birthday, Awu's birthday...
We even tried your phone number.
It must include Awu's.
We tried Awu's.
Awu.
Trust me.
It definitely includes Awu's.
It's open.
What was the code?
Awu's birthday plus mine.
That makes sense.
I keep my most important things in here, I...
The dashcam.
I think this
will definitely help with Xiao Lu's case.
Take it for now.
No matter what the final result is,
please let me know right away.
I have no choice.
With my current condition,
this is as far as I can help you.
Thank you.
What is this?
These are...
This is a memory card I recorded for Awu.
For his coming-of-age ceremony,
his college graduation,
his wedding,
and when he becomes a father.
I'm afraid
I won't have the chance to be there for these milestones,
so I
recorded some things for him.
I'm begging you,
when these
moments arrive,
please play them for him
to watch.
Don't peek beforehand.
The harmonica Awu gave me.
Have a look.
These are...
They are just some bank cards.
There should be some savings on them.
They are left for Awu.
What is this?
This...
Right.
Do you remember?
Didn't I tell you
that we were going to open a law firm?
Take a look.
I thought you...
I thought you were just doing that to
get me to report the Sham Litigation Factory.
What? I was serious.
I looked at a lot of offices.
I think its location,
size, and rent are
all quite ideal.
So,
I rented it first.
I'm just waiting for you to
finish up everything you're dealing with right now,
then I'll ask for your opinion.
If you agree,
I will
actually
sign a long-term lease for it.
I'm on a short-term contract right now,
renting it for half a year.
This safe is just to keep some
things that are relatively important to me.
That's good then.
Now I'm no longer afraid of
forgetting the password.
Because I have you to remember it for me.
Yang A'wu and you
are now
the most important people to me.
Was adopting Yang A'wu
really just to tie down Yu Songfan?
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
Deadbeats.
They stick to the Three-No Principle.
No appearances, no repayments, no responses.
To them, court documents
are nothing more
than elementary school sick notes.
You have no idea
how bizarre their excuses for not appearing are.
"The client has become a monk."
Civil cases sure are interesting.
I remember when I first joined the firm,
I assisted you with a case.
In the end,
we found out the plaintiff and the defendant
were actually having an affair.
Do you still remember?
I remember.
When they face off in court,
they're fighting a lawsuit,
but what they're paying back
is emotional debt.
Drink up.
Ding Ning.
What's wrong?
Am I not welcome?
What are you talking about?
Come on, have a seat.
Why are you here?
Open it yourself.
Did you run away from home, from Yu Songfan's place?
Can't I just come to see you?
Sit down.
Miracles do happen.
Am I really that unfeeling in your eyes?
I just feel that
everyone has been really good to me.
You've learned how to play the emotional card.
No, why are you all looking at me?
Keep talking.
Don't you think this scene is super familiar?
We joined Chang Yu on the same day.
It was the two of us, also at night.
Mentor made us stay behind.
That awkward welcome party.
It was so shabby.
There was a banner hanging over there.
What did it say again?
Right, right.
Rising legal stars.
Changyu Law Firm,
renewed and upgraded.
But after taking the banner down,
it said underneath,
For Dream Chasers.
Let youth blow through your long hair,
let it guide your dreams.
Stop it.
Let's not bring up the past.
It was supposed to celebrate us joining,
but it ended up turning into
Mentor's one-man talk show.
All that talk about ideals and beliefs.
He had too much to drink that day.
Do you remember?
After you got drunk,
you put your arm around my neck
and force-fed me Chicken soup for the soul.
I was so embarrassed.
I had no choice.
He was the boss, I had to humor him.
I was just a workplace newbie.
I kept glancing at you,
hoping you would chime in
and save me.
But her,
she just kept her head down,
eating quietly by herself.
She didn't even look up once.
I was embarrassed too.
I couldn't just ask for trouble, could I?
Come on.
See?
That's just how it is.
We've come full circle.
When I was young,
I was focused on working hard to move up
and making something of myself.
But later on,
I hit a wall and grew.
Hit another wall, grew some more.
In the blink of an eye,
over a dozen years went by,
and I just lived an unremarkable life.
Who I am today
is completely different from what I imagined.
But when I really think about it,
being able to interact
with the neighbors from time to time
actually makes me feel quite at ease.
Living an ordinary life every day...
I'm quite satisfied with it.
Minor civil cases
deal with social complexities.
Major criminal cases involve
the safety of family and nation.
In fact, both of these
are very important.
As long as you work steadily,
you can achieve great things
and become a valuable lawyer.
You're young,
so don't be afraid of trial and error.
Once you go further and experience more,
you'll come to understand
that everyone
has a place that suits them.
Mentor,
I want to come back.
Thank you, Mentor.
Mentor.
Ding Ning.
Stick to the path you've chosen.
Come back and visit often.
Don't worry, Mentor.
I will.
I'll drink to that too.
Let youth blow through your long hair
Let it guide your dreams
Unknowingly, the history of this city
Has already remembered your smile
Then I'll come back to work next Monday.
No pay raise.
Same desk.
Hello. Do you have an appointment?
Yes, I do.
Ms. Yang, please wait a moment.
This box blocks all signals.
Phones, trackers, bugs, etc.
So I don't need to say more.
I won't bother with a pat-down.
When meeting the elders,
make sure you don't play tricks.
If anything goes wrong,
even I won't be able to protect you.
Hold on.
Is this a bug
or a tracker or something?
Such a sneaky little trick
doesn't seem like Yu Songfan's idea.
Was it you?
Just keep driving.
Yes, sir.
It's gone.
Ding Ning's signal dropped.
He wants to use you
to wear away the last of my faith,
and turn me completely into him.
This is a long-range tracking and listening device.
If you're really that worried,
you can use this to find me.
Find out
which road the signal disappeared on.
Got it.
Found it.
Near this road,
there are three locations of interest.
An abandoned stadium,
the old cave wine cellar,
and the farm.
They're here.
Let's go.
Well, well.
Starting the party without me?
Mr. Bi.
They're here.
Ding Ning.
This is Mr. Bi.